Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Boeing Aerospace Board, 1962-63 - Boston Edison Co., 3/6/61 (Box 40-42)
  - Boston Daily Newspapers, Boston, Mass. And Boston Typographical Union, Local 13, 1967 (Box 40-42, Folder 26)
  - Boston Daily Newspapers, Boston, Mass. And Boston Typographical Union, Local 13, 1967 (Box 40-42, Folder 27)
  - Boston Edison Co., Boston Mass. And Utility Workers Local 387, 1952 (Box 40-42, Folder 28)
  - Boston Edison Co., Boston Mass. And Utility Workers Local 369, 1953 (Box 40-42, Folder 29)
  - Boston Edison Co., Boston Mass. And Utility Workers Local 369, 1954 (Box 40-42, Folder 30)
  - Boston Edison Co., Boston Mass. And Utility Workers Local 369, 1957 (Box 40-42, Folder 31)
  - Boston Edison Co., Boston Mass. And Utility Workers Local 387, 1961 (Box 40-42, Folder 32)
- Boston Edison Co., 12/7/62 - Bridgeport Rubber Co., 10/27/58 (Box 43-45)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union Local 369 (43-1), 1962 (Box 43-45, Folder 1)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Local 386, 1963 (Box 43-45, Folder 2)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union, Local 136, 1964 (Box 43-45, Folder 3)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union Local 386, 1965 (Box 43-45, Folder 4)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union Local 369 (43-5), 1966 (Box 43-45, Folder 5)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union: Briefs and Miscellaneous Information (Box 43-45, Folder 6)
  - Utility Workers Local 836 and Boston Edison Co., Stenographic Record pg. 1-224 (43-7) (Box 43-45, Folder 7)
  - Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union Local 369, Stenographic Record (43-8) (Box 43-45, Folder 8)
  - Boston Elevated Railway Company and IBEW Local 104 (44-1), 1946 (Box 43-45, Folder 9)
  - Boston Gas Company and United Mine Workers Local 12003, 12118 (44-2), 1961 (Box 43-45, Folder 10)
  - Boston Gas Company and United Mine Workers District 50 (44-3), 1967 (Box 43-45, Folder 11)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers, Local 4335 (44-4), 1953 (Box 43-45, Folder 12)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers, CIO (44-5), 1953 (Box 43-45, Folder 13)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-6), 1955 (Box 43-45, Folder 14)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-7), 1956 (Box 43-45, Folder 15)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-8), 1957 (Box 43-45, Folder 16)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-9), 1957 (Box 43-45, Folder 17)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-10), 1959 (Box 43-45, Folder 18)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-11), 1962 (Box 43-45, Folder 19)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers of America (44-12), 1963 (Box 43-45, Folder 20)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-13), 1964 (Box 43-45, Folder 21)
  - Boston Gear Works and United Steelworkers Local 4335 (44-14), 1966 (Box 43-45, Folder 22)
  - Boston Globe and Boston Typographical Union No. 13 (44-15), 1965 (Box 43-45, Folder 23)
  - Boston and Lockport Block and International Association of Machinist Lodge 38 (45-1), 1963 (Box 43-45, Folder 24)
  - Boston and Lockport Block and International Association of Machinist Lodge 264 (45-2), 1965 (Box 43-45, Folder 25)
  - Boston & Maine Railroad and Brotherhood of Railway & Steamship Clerks (45-3), 1960 (Box 43-45, Folder 26)
  - Boston Record-American Advertiser and Newspaper Guild of Boston (45-4), 1956 (Box 43-45, Folder 27)
  - Boston Record-American Advertisement and American Federation of Newswriters (45-5), 1968 (Box 43-45, Folder 28)
  - Boston Retail Clothiers Group and Clothing Workers Local 335 (45-6), 1951 (Box 43-45, Folder 29)
  - Boston Sand & Gravel Company and Teamsters Local 379 (45-7), 1967 (Box 43-45, Folder 30)
  - Bradford Spinning Company and Textile Workers Local 604 (45-8), 1948 (Box 43-45, Folder 31)
  - Bridgeport Gas Company and United Mine Workers Local 12298 (45-9), 1967 (Box 43-45, Folder 32)
  - Bridgeport Rubber Co. and Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, & Plastic Workers Local 176 (45-10), 1958 (Box 43-45, Folder 33)
- Brockton, Mass., Vampers Local Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsman, 9/23/54 - Budd Co., 9/7/67 (Box 46-48)
  - Brockton, Mass. Vampers Local, Shoe and Allied Craftsmen and Stitchers Local, Shoe and Alled Craftsmen and Stitchers Local, Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1954-1955 (Box 46-48, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Hearing, 1953 (Box 46-48, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Hearing, 1953 (Box 46-48, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Hearing, 1953 (Box 46-48, Folder 4)
  - Confidential File, 1954 (Box 46-48, Folder 5)
  - Associated Shoe Industries of Southeastern Mass. And Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1955 (Box 46-48, Folder 6)
  - Brockway-Smith-Haigh-Lowell, Charleston, Mass. And Teamster Local 379, 1964 (Box 46-48, Folder 7)
  - Homer D. Bronson Co., Beacon Falls Conn. And United Steelworkers, 1960 (Box 46-48, Folder 8)
  - Homer D. Bronson Co., Beacon Falls Conn. And United Steel Workers, 1963 (Box 46-48, Folder 9)
  - Brown Brothers Co., Gardner, Mass. And United Furniture Workers, Local 154, 1946 (Box 46-48, Folder 10)
  - Brown Company, Berlin, N.H. and United Mine Workers, Dist. 50. Local 12175, 1947 (Box 46-48, Folder 11)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co., Providence, R.I. and Office Employees Int'l., Local 76, 1947 (Box 46-48, Folder 12)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co., Providence, R.I. and Office Employees Int'l., Local 76, 1949 (Box 46-48, Folder 13)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co., Providence, R.I. and Office Employees Int'l., Local 76, 1954 (Box 46-48, Folder 14)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co., Providence, R.I. and Office Employees Int'l., Local 76, 1954 (Box 46-48, Folder 15)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co., Providence, R.I. and Office Employees Int'l., Local 76, 1954 (Box 46-48, Folder 16)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co and Am. Fed. Of Technical Engineers, Loc. 119, 1954 (Box 46-48, Folder 17)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co and Am. Fed. Of Technical Engineers, Loc. 119, 1954 (Box 46-48, Folder 18)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co and Am. Fed. Of Technical Engineers, Loc. 119, 1957 (Box 46-48, Folder 19)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co and Am. Fed. Of Technical Engineers, Loc. 119, 1966 (Box 46-48, Folder 20)
  - G.L. Brownell, Inc., Worcester, Mas. And United Steelworkers Local 2936, 1957 (Box 46-48, Folder 21)
  - Brunswick-Union, Inc., Torrington, Conn. Int'l Union of Electrical Workers Local 247, 1963 (Box 46-48, Folder 22)
  - Bryant Chucking Grinder Co., Springfield, Vermont and United Electrical Workers, Local 218, 1946 (Box 46-48, Folder 23)
  - The Budd Company, Philadelphia, Pa. and United Automobile Workers Local 813, 1967 (Box 46-48, Folder 24)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and Textile Workers, Local 1093, 1961 (Box 46-48, Folder 25)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and Textile Workers, Local 1093, 1961 (Box 46-48, Folder 26)
- Building Service Employees International Union, Local 7, 5/11/62 - Celanese Corp. of America, Celviver Plant, 3/10/61 (Box 49-51)
  - Building Service Employees, Local 1 and Building Service Employees, Local 4, 1962 (Box 49-51, Folder 1)
    April 11, 1962
  - Butler Aviation Company, Boston, Massachusetts and International Association of Machinists, District 147, 1966 (Box 49-51, Folder 2)
    September 12, 1966
  - Campbell Soup Company, Camden, New Jersey and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2031, 1967 (Box 49-51, Folder 3)
    February 27, 1967
  - S.W. Card Manufacturing Company, Mansfield, Massachusetts and United Steelworkers, Local 3955, 1956 (Box 49-51, Folder 4)
    December 31, 1956
  - S.W. Card Manufacturing Company, Division Union Twist Drill and United Steelworkers. Local 3955, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 5)
    September 23, 1958
  - S.W. Card Manufacturing Company, Division Union Twist Drill and United Steelworkers. Local 3955, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 6)
    October 2, 1958
  - S.W. Card Manufacturing Company, Division Union Twist Drill and United Steelworkers. Local 3955, 1961 (Box 49-51, Folder 7)
    February 20, 1961
  - Carlyle Johnson Machine Company, Manchester, Connecticut and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 281, 1965 (Box 49-51, Folder 8)
    November 22, 1965
  - Carr Leather Company, Peabody, Massachusetts and Fur Leather Workers Union, Local 21, 1946 (Box 49-51, Folder 9)
    July 17, 1946
  - Carr Leather Company, Peabody, Massachusetts and Fur Leather Workers Union, Local 21, 1951 (Box 49-51, Folder 10)
    May 14, 1951
  - Carr Manufacturing Company, Bristol, Rhode Island and United Rubber Workers, Local 474, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 11)
    January 6, 1958
  - Carrier Corporation, Syracuse, New York and Sheet Metal Workers International, Local 527, 1964-1965 (Box 49-51, Folder 12)
  - Carrier Corporation, Syracuse, New York and Sheet Metal Workers International, Local 527, 1965 (Box 49-51, Folder 13)
    November 10, 1965
  - Carriers Employers Association, Sanborn, Incorporated, and Quinn, Incorporated; and Truck Drivers, Local 340, 1965 (Box 49-51, Folder 14)
    January 18, 1965
  - Caterpillar Tractor Company, Joliet, Illinois and International Association of Machinists, Local 851, 1967 (Box 49-51, Folder 15)
    November 28, 1967
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 16)
    March 24, 1958
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 17)
    March 25, 1958
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 18)
    May 22, 1958
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 19)
    May 23, 1958
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1958 (Box 49-51, Folder 20)
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1959 (Box 49-51, Folder 21)
    August 11, 1959
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1959 (Box 49-51, Folder 22)
    October 1959
  - CBS - Hytron, Danvers, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 270, 1960-1961 (Box 49-51, Folder 23)
  - Celanese Corporation, Celriver Plant, South Carolina and Textile Workers, Local 1093, 1956 (Box 49-51, Folder 24)
    July 26, 1956
  - Celanese Corporation, Celriver Plant, South Carolina and Textile Workers, Local 1093, 1956 (Box 49-51, Folder 25)
    October 29, 1956
  - Celanese Corporation, Narrows, Virginia and United Construction Workers, Local 15153, 1960 (Box 49-51, Folder 26)
    August 26, 1960
  - Celanese Corporation, Celriver Plant, South Carolina and Textile Workers, Local 1093, 1961 (Box 49-51, Folder 27)
    March 10, 1961
- Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers Co., 3/13/61 - Cheney Bigelow Works (Box 52-54)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and Textile Workers Local 1093, 1962 (Box 52-54, Folder 1)
  - Celanese Corp., Celriver Plant, S.C. and Textile Workers Local 1093, 1962 (Box 52-54, Folder 2)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and Textile Workers Local 1093, 1962 (Box 52-54, Folder 3)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and Textile Workers Local 1093, 1962 (Box 52-54, Folder 4)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and United Mine Workers Local 1093, 1962 (Box 52-54, Folder 5)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and United Mine Workers Local 15153, 1964 (Box 52-54, Folder 6)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and United Mine Workers Local 15153, 1964 (Box 52-54, Folder 7)
  - Celanese Corp., Celanese Fibers, S.C. and Textile Workers, Local 1093, 1966 (Box 52-54, Folder 8)
  - Celluplastic Corp., Fitchburg, Mass. And Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Local 875, 1959 (Box 52-54, Folder 9)
  - Cello-Products Company, Swarthmore, Pa. and Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 339, 1964 (Box 52-54, Folder 10)
  - Central Leather Company, Peabody, Mass. And Fur and Leathers Workers, Local 21, 1947 (Box 52-54, Folder 11)
  - Central Leather Company, Peabody, Mass. And Fur and Leathers Workers, Local 21, 1950 (Box 52-54, Folder 12)
  - Central Leather Company, Peabody, Mass. And Fur and Leathers Workers, Local 21, 1950 (Box 52-54, Folder 13)
  - Central Leather Company, Peabody, Mass. And Fur and Leathers Workers, Local 21, 1951 (Box 52-54, Folder 14)
  - Central Leather Company, Peabody, Mass. And Fur and Leathers Workers, Local 21, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 15)
  - Chain Belt Co., Baldwin-Duckworth Div. and United Steelworkers Local 4559, 1954 (Box 52-54, Folder 16)
  - Champion Lamp Works, Div. Consolidated Electric Lamp Co. and United Electrical Workers, Local 215, 1946 (Box 52-54, Folder 17)
  - Chance Vought Aircraft, United Aircraft and United Auto Workers, Local 893, 1953 (Box 52-54, Folder 18)
  - Chandler Evans Corp., W. Hartford, Conn. And United Auto Workers, Local 405, 1961 (Box 52-54, Folder 19)
  - Chandler Evans Corp., W. Hartford, Conn. And United Auto Workers, Local 405, 1963 (Box 52-54, Folder 20)
  - Chandler Evans Corp., W. Hartford, Conn. And United Auto Workers, Local 405, 1963 (Box 52-54, Folder 21)
  - Chandler Evans Corp., W. Hartford, Conn. And United Auto Workers, Local 405, 1967 (Box 52-54, Folder 22)
  - Chase Brass and Copper Co., Waterbury, Conn. And Chase Brass and Copper Workers, UAW Local 1565, 1951 (Box 52-54, Folder 23)
  - Chase Brass and Copper Co., Waterbury, Conn. And Chase Brass and Copper Workers, UAW Local 1565, 1953 (Box 52-54, Folder 24)
  - Chase Brass and Copper Co., Waterbury, Conn. And Chase Brass and Copper Workers, UAW Local 1565, 1957 (Box 52-54, Folder 25)
  - Chase Brass and Copper Co., Waterbury, Conn. And Chase Brass and Copper Workers, UAW Local 1565, 1961 (Box 52-54, Folder 26)
  - Chemetron Corp., Searsport, Maine Int'l Chemical Workers Local 650, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 27)
  - Chemetron Corp., Searsport, Maine Int'l Chemical Workers Local 650, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 28)
  - Chemetron Corp., Searsport, Maine Int'l Chemical Workers Local 650, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 29)
  - Chemetron Corp., Searsport, Maine Int'l Chemical Workers Local 650, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 30)
  - Chemetron Corp., Searsport, Maine Int'l Chemical Workers Local 650, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 31)
  - Chemetron Corp., Searsport, Maine Int'l Chemical Workers Local 650, 1960 (Box 52-54, Folder 32)
  - Cheney Bigelow Wire Works, Mass. And American Wire Weavers Protective Assoc., 1953 (Box 52-54, Folder 33)
- Chicago Pneumatic Tool Co., It/13/59 - Consolidated Thermo-Plastics Co., Turex Div., 11/15/65, 3/9/66 (Box 55-57)
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company, Utica, New York and International Association of Machinists, Local 645, 1959 (Box 55-57, Folder 1)
    April 13, 1959
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company, Utica, New York and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 645, 1959 (Box 55-57, Folder 2)
    July 17, 1959
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company, Utica, New York and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 55-57, Folder 3)
    December 23, 1959
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company, Utica, New York and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1961 (Box 55-57, Folder 4)
    April 7, 1961
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company, Utica, New York and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1961 (Box 55-57, Folder 5)
    April 10, 1961
  - Cities Transportation Company, Nashua, New Hampshire and Teamsters, Local 633, 1947 (Box 55-57, Folder 6)
    April 17, 1947
  - Clarostat Manufacturing Company, Dover, New Hampshire and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 242, 1954 (Box 55-57, Folder 7)
    August 13, 1954
  - Claussner Hosiery Company, Paducah, Kentucky and American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1959 (Box 55-57, Folder 8)
    March 6, 1959
  - Clifford Manufacturing Company, Waltham, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 274, 1953 (Box 55-57, Folder 9)
    March 2, 1953
  - Clifford Manufacturing Company, Waltham, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 274, 1956 (Box 55-57, Folder 10)
    July 9, 1956
  - Clifford Manufacturing Company, Waltham, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 274, 1957 (Box 55-57, Folder 11)
    January 28, 1957
  - Clifford Manufacturing Company, Standard Thomson Corporation, and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 274, 1960 (Box 55-57, Folder 12)
    April 10, 1960
  - Clifford Manufacturing Company, Waltham, Massachusetts and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 274, 1960 (Box 55-57, Folder 13)
    November 14, 1960
  - Coca Cola Bottling Company of Boston and Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union 513, 1949 (Box 55-57, Folder 14)
    August 1949
  - Cogsdill Twist Drill Company, Greenfield, Massachusetts and United Electrical Workers, Local 274, 1961 (Box 55-57, Folder 15)
    November 27, 1961
  - Cohu Electronics, Incorporated, Massa Division, Massachusetts and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 38, 1963 (Box 55-57, Folder 16)
    October 8, 1963
  - Coleman Brothers and Teamsters, 1965 (Box 55-57, Folder 17)
  - Collyer Wire Company, Pawtucket, Rhode Island and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1950 (Box 55-57, Folder 18)
    December 1, 1950
  - Colonial Tanning Company, Incorporated, Boston, Massachusetts and Leather Workers International, Local 56, 1962 (Box 55-57, Folder 19)
    March 26, 1962
  - Colt's Patent Firearms Company, Hartford, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, 1946 (Box 55-57, Folder 20)
    May 6, 1946
  - Colt's Patent Firearms Company, Hartford, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, 1946 (Box 55-57, Folder 21)
    May 9, 1946
  - Colt's Patent Firearms Company, Hartford, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, 1946 (Box 55-57, Folder 22)
    May 13, 1946
  - Colt's Patent Firearms Company, Hartford, Connecticut and Colt's Local Union 270, 1946 (Box 55-57, Folder 23)
    April 23, 1946
  - Colt's Patent Firearms Company, Hartford, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, 1946 (Box 55-57, Folder 24)
    May 15, 1946
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, New York, New York and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1212, 1966 (Box 55-57, Folder 25)
    May 3, 1966
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, New York, New York and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1212, 1967 (Box 55-57, Folder 26)
    August 24, 1967
  - Columbia Packing Company, Boston, Massachusetts and United Packinghouse Workers Local 11, 1953 (Box 55-57, Folder 27)
    October 20, 1953
  - Columbia Packing Company, Boston, Massachusetts and United Packinghouse Workers Local 11, 1953 (Box 55-57, Folder 28)
    October 29, 1953
  - Columbia Records, Bridgeport, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, Local 237, 1957 (Box 55-57, Folder 29)
    April 24, 1957
  - Columbia Records, Bridgeport, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, Local 237, 1959 (Box 55-57, Folder 30)
    May 14, 1959
  - Columbia Records, Bridgeport, Connecticut and United Electrical Workers, Local 237, 1963 (Box 55-57, Folder 31)
    May 13, 1963
  - Combustion Engineering and Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers Local 558, 1966 (Box 55-57, Folder 32)
    September 1, 1966
  - Commonwealth Plastics Corporation, Massachusetts and Plastic Workers, Department Store Union, 1960 (Box 55-57, Folder 33)
    November 29, 1960
  - The Connecticut Company and Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach, 1946-1947 (Box 55-57, Folder 34)
    November 25, 1946 and April 28, 1947
  - Connecticut Light and Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local B-420, 1948 (Box 55-57, Folder 35)
    April 28, 1948
  - Connecticut Ready Mixed Concrete Association, Incorporated and Teamsters, Local 559 of Joint Council, 1964 (Box 55-57, Folder 36)
    November 19, 1964
  - Connecticut River Mills, Charlestown, New Hampshire and Textile Workers, Local 94, 1947 (Box 55-57, Folder 37)
    February 21, 1947
  - Connecticut Telephone and Electric Corporation and United Electrical Workers, Local 285, 1954 (Box 55-57, Folder 38)
    April 3, 1954
  - Connecticut Telephone and Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 285, 1954 (Box 55-57, Folder 39)
    April 24, 1954
  - Consolidated Chemical Industries, Massachusetts and Fur and Leather Workers Union (Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1948 (Box 55-57, Folder 40)
    December 27, 1948
  - Consolidated Chemical Company and Fur and Leather Workers Union, Local 295, 1953 (Box 55-57, Folder 41)
    May 12, 1953
  - Consolidated Diesel Electric Corporation, Connecticut and United Auto Workers, Local 529, 1966 (Box 55-57, Folder 42)
    April 14, 1966
  - Consolidated Thermoplastics Company, Rhode Island and Steelworkers, Local 6535, 1965-1966 (Box 55-57, Folder 43)
    November 15, 1965 and March 9, 1966
- Container Corp. of America, 4/12/67 - Coro Inc. Eastern Jewerly Mfg. Co., 6/9/49 (Box 58-60)
  - Continental Airlines, Inc., Los Angeles and Air Line Pilots Association, 1966 (Box 58-60, Folder 1)
  - Container Corporation of America and Papermakers and Paper workers, Local 68, 1967 (Box 58-60, Folder 2)
  - Continental Airlines, Chicago, Illinois and Flight Hostesses, Pilots Assoc., 1966 (Box 58-60, Folder 3)
  - Continental Tanning Co., Lynn Mass. And Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 20L, 1960 (Box 58-60, Folder 4)
  - Continental Tanning Co., Lynn Mass. And Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 20L, 1963 (Box 58-60, Folder 5)
  - Converter Corp., Leominster, Mass. And Chemical Workers Union, Local 533, 1965 (Box 58-60, Folder 6)
  - Cornell-Dubilier Electric Corp., Mass. And IBEW, Local 410, 1964 (Box 58-60, Folder 7)
  - Cornish Wire Co., Williamstown, Mass. And International Union of Electrical Workers Local 299, 1961 (Box 58-60, Folder 8)
  - Cornish Wire Co., Williamstown, Mass. And International Union of Electrical Workers Local 299, 1967 (Box 58-60, Folder 9)
  - Coro, Inc., Eastern Jewelry Mfg. Co., R.I. and Int'l Jewelry Workers, Local 66, 1949 (Box 58-60, Folder 10)
- Coro, Inc. Eastern Jewerly Mfg. Co., 5/31/50 - Crestbrand Tanning Co., 4/9/56 (Box 61)
  - Coro, Inc., Eastern Jewelry Mfg. Co., R.I. and Int'l. Jewelry Workers, Local 18, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration on Alex Tamarro and James De Filippo, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Coty, Inc. and Coty Products Corp. and Teamsters, Local 815, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Courier Citizen Printing Co., Mass. Lowell Typographical Union, Local 310, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - B.E. Cox Leather Co., Peabody, Mass. And Fur Leather Workers, Local 21, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Cox Leather Co., Peabody, Mass. And Fur and Leather Workers, Local 21, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - B.E. Cox Leather Co., Mass. And International Fur and Leather Workers, Local 21, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Cranston Print Works, Cranston, R.I. and Textile Workers, Local 2459, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Cranston Print Works, Cranston, R.I. and Textile Workers, Local 2459, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Cranston Print Works, Cranston, R.I. and Textile Workers, Local 2459, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Creese and Cook Co., Danvers, Mass. And Fur and Leather Workers, Local 21, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Cranston Print Works, Cranston, R.I. and Textile Workers, Local 2459, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Creese and Cook Co., Danvers, Mass. And Fur and Leather Workers, Local 21, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Creese and Cook Co., Danvers, Mass. And Fur and Leather Workers, Local 21, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Creese and Cook Co., Danvers, Mass. And Fur and Leather Workers, Local 21, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 15)